Guide to the Francis C. Moon papers, 1961-2009.
Moon, Francis C. papers
- Series VIII. 16mm Films
  - NASA Bearing, c. 1990; F-1033 (Box 6)
    Creator: KC Dufe
  - Mag. Buckling, F-1034 (Box 6)
    Snap Buckling of a Beam Near a Perm Mag, Snap Buckling of Ferromag Beam in a Mag Field, Helical Curr Ele in a Coaxial Mag Field, Firing the Beer Can, Buckling of Superconducting Mag in a Torus.
  - Torus, Mag Lev, and Chaos, F-1035 (Box 6)
    Torus (1 minute), Mag Lev (3 Minutes cut out for Japan file), Chaos: 1 Degree of Freedom (11:15), 2 Degrees of Freedom (14 minutes).
  - Levitating Trains, F-1036 (Box 6)
  - 16 Coil Torus?, F-1037 (Box 6)
  - Mag Buck Arch, F-1038 (Box 6)
- Series IX. Mag-Lev Transportation Conference Proceedings
  - International Conference on Maglev and Linear Drives, May 14-16, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Location: Vancouver, BC Canada
  - The IUTAM Symposium on The Electro-Magnetical Interactions in Deformable Solids and Structures, October 12-17, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Location: Tokyo, Japan
  - Linear Electric Machines, October 21-23, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Location: London, England
  - 1981 Conference on the Computation of Magnetic Fields - Compumag, March, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Location: Chicago, Illinois
  - 13th International Symposium on Electromagnetic Launch, May 22-25, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Location: Berlin, Germany
    IEEE Transactions on Magnetics
  - Planning the Transrapid Berlin-Hamburg (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Location: Berlin-Hamburg, Germany
    Brochure
  - The 15th International Conference on Magnetically Levitated Systems and Linear Drives, April 12-15, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Location: Yamanashi, Japan
  - The Second International Symposium on Linear Drives for Industry Applications, April 8-10, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Maglev 2000, The 16th International Conference on Magnetically Levitated Systems and Linear Drives, June 7-10, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Location: Rio de Janiero, Brazil
  - Superconducting Maglev Technology (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - HSST: A Totally New Concept in Riding Comfort (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Proceedings of the 2nd International Workshop on Electromagnetic Forces and Related Effects on Blankets and Other Structures Surrounding the Fusion Plasma Torus, September 15-17, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Location: Tokai, Ibaraki, Japan
  - 4th International Symposium on Super-Conductivity, October 14-17, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1980 Digests of the Intermag Conference, International Magnetics Conference, April 21-24, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Location: Boston, Mass.
  - The First International Symposium on Linear Drives for Industry Applications, May 31-June 2, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Location: Nagasaki, Japan
  - International Conference on Maglev Transport '85, September 17-19, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Second International Seminar on Superconductive Magnetic Levitated Train, November 4-5, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Location: Miyasaki, Japan
  - International Seminar on Super-Conductive Magnetic Levitated Train Superconductor Industry, November 9-10, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Superconductor Industry, Fall, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Applied Superconductivity Technology of Toshiba, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Brochure written in Japanese with Pictures
- Series X. Kinetic Sculpture Course Files
  - Miscellaneous Materials Relating to Kinetic Sculpture, A (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Includes: "Catalog of Audiokinetic Sculptures", "Mechanism Design Analysis and Synthesis", "Sculpture Since 1945", Articles and miscellaneous notes
  - Miscellaneous Materials Relating to Kinetic Sculpture, B (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Includes: Drawings of Kinetic Sculptures, Assembly order for Kinetic Sculptures, Kinetic Sculpture Midterm Exam Spring 1998, "Aerodynamics, Aeronautics, and Flight Mechanics", "George Rickey in Berlin"
  - Miscellaneous Materials Relating to Kinetic Sculpture, C (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Includes: "Beasts on High", drawings of Kinetic Sculptures, "Andy Goldsworthy at Storm King Art Center", "Computers in Art and Design".
  - Kinetic Art and Chaos (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Includes: Emails from Ken Hover, notes.
  - Kinetic Sculpture Book Proposal (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Includes: "Principles of Kinetic Sculpture" Chapter outline, other notes.
  - Kinetic Sculpture Project Ideas (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Includes: Notes and Drawings.
  - Kinetic Sculpture Articles (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Includes: Fine Arts Library Reserve Request Form, Search Request.
  - Chaotic and Dynamic Toys and Sculpture (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Includes: Photos and slides, emails, articles, and notes.
  - Kinetic Sculpture (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Includes: "Chronology of Kinetic Art".
  - Kinetic Sculpture Lecture Notes (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Includes: Variety of notes and drawings, "Aerodynamics, Aeronautics, and Flight Mechanics," Notes on the videotape Nonlinear Dynamics and Chaos: Lab Demonstrations by Steven H. Strogatz, Chaotic Waterwheel, Double Pendulum, Howard Stone and other demonstrations.
  - Kinetic Sculpture Artists (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Includes: Storm King Art Center brochure, The Donald M. Kendall Sculpture Gardens Brochure, notes and articles.
  - George Rhoads/Rock Stream Studies, Ithaca (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Includes: Notes, articles, and variety of materials relating to George Rhoads.
- Series XI. Mag-Lev Research and Reports
  - A Critical Examination of the Literature on the Biological Effects of Extremely Low Frequency and Extremely High Frequency (Box 8)
    Author: Jelinski, L.W.
  - Noise Criteria for High Speed Maglev, September, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Hanson, C.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Federal Railroad Administration
  - Recommendations for Acoustical Test Facility for Maglev Research, September, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Maglev Revisted: Is Everybody Ready This Time?, 1991 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Transportation-MIT
  - Report on Travel to Japan, August, 1988 (Box 8)
    Author: Rote, D., Johnson, L.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: 1st International Symposium on Superconductivity in Nagoya Magnetically Levitated Vehicle Research…
  - Maglev Program Test Plan, Apri, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: deBenedet, D.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: National Maglev Initiative, Second Technology Symposium, Argonne National Laboratory
  - Misc. Papers, Notes, Talks on MagLev, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - MagLev- Japan, 1998 (Box 8)
  - The Greatest Show on Earth, 1973 (Box 8)
    Author: Basta, N.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: The Princeton Engineer
  - Measurement and Analysis of Magnetic and Electric Fields for Existing and Advanced Rail Transportation Systems (Box 8)
    Author: Dietrich, F., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Research and Management, Inc.
  - Maglev-Rail Intermodal Equipment & Suspension, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Gilcrease, E., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: National Maglev Initiative 2nd BAA/SCD Symposium, Argonne National Laboratory
  - Conceptual Requirement of the Superconducting Linear Induction Motor, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Hennessy, M., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Argonne
  - Assessment of Maglev Guideway Systems (Box 8)
    Author: Gangarao, H., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: USDOT- FRA US Army Corps of Engineers
  - High Performance Low Cost Guideway, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Kokkins, S., Et al
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: National Maglev Initiative Symposium
  - Parametric Studies of Suspension and Propulsion Subsystems, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Yang, F.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Second BAA/SCD Technology Symposium, Argonne National Laboratory
  - Very Fast Trains are Feasible, But Costly, 1991 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: National Research Council NewsReport
  - Guideway Structural Design and Power/Propulsion/Braking in Relation to Guideways, Appendix A, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: The Maglev 2000 Team
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: USDOT- FRA
  - Guideway Structural Design and Power/Propulsion/Braking in Relation to Guideways, Appendix B, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Guideway Structural Design and Power/Propulsion/Braking in Relation to Guideways, Final Report, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Maglev Technology Assessment Symposium, 1991 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: USDOT-FRA, US Army Corps of Engineers, USDoE
  - Noise From High Speed Maglev Systems, 1993 (Box 8)
    Author: Hanson, C., Et al
  - Low Cost Guideways For Maglev, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Thornton, R
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Argonne Laboratory
  - Parametric Studies of Suspension and Propulsion Subsystems, 1991 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: 1st BAA Conference, Cambridge, Mass.
  - Adaptive Suspension Using Electrorheological Fluids (Box 8)
    Author: Bhadra, D.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: General Atomics
  - Guideway Sensor Systems, 1998 (Box 8)
    Author: Bower, J,
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Babcock and Wilson
  - Novel Cryogen-free Actively Shielded Superconducting Magnets for Mag-Lev Vehicles, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Vermilyea, M.E.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: GE for USDOT/FRA/NMI
  - Low Cost Guideways For Maglev, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Phelan, R.S., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: MIT for USDOT/NMI
  - Application of Cable-In-Conduit Conductor to Maglev Magnet Systems, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Thome, R.J., Et al
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: DOT/FRA/NMI
  - Maglev Economic Analysis, 1991 (Box 8)
    Author: Mongini, A.
  - The National Maglev Initiative Strategic Plan, 1991 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: NMI
  - Results From Argonne's Maglev Activities, 1991 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Argonne National Laboratory
  - Present Status of Computational Tools for Maglev Development, 1991 (Box 8)
    Author: Wang, Z., Et al
  - Assessment of the Potential for Magnetic Levitation Transportation Systems in the United States, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Assessment of the Potential for Magnetic Levitation Transportation Systems in the United States (Report Supplement), 1990 (Box 8)
  - Conceptual Design and Analysis of the Tracked Magnetically Levitated Vehicle Technology Program (TMLV)-Repulsion Scheme Executive Summary, 1975 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Ford Motor Co. for USDOT- FRA
  - Maglev-Rail Intermodal Equipment and Suspension Study, 1993 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Parsons Brinckerhoff Quade & Douglas for USDOT
  - Sensor Systems for Monitoring Maglev Guideway Structures, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Berthold, J.W., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Babcock and Wilson for NMI
  - Maglev Guideway and Route Integrity Requirements, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Carlton, S., Et al
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Martin Marietta Corporation for NMI
  - Dynamic Characteristics of Magnetically Levitated Vehicle Systems (Box 8)
    Author: Cai, Y., Chen, S.S.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Energy Technology Division, Argonne National Laboratory
  - Applications of Superconductor Technologies to Transportation, 1989 (Box 8)
    Author: Rote, D.M., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Energy and Environmental Systems Division
  - Dynamic Stability of Repulsive-Force Maglev Suspension Systems, 1996 (Box 8)
    Author: Cai, Y., Et al.
  - The Use of Superconducting Magnets for Suspension and Guidance in High Speed Ground Transportation, 1968 (Box 8)
    Author: Coffey, H.T., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Stanford Research Institute
  - Dynamic Stability Experiment of Maglev Systems, 1995 (Box 8)
  - A Review of Dynamic Characteristics of Magnetically Levitated Vehicle Systems, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Magnetic Levitation Vehicle-Suspension Guideway Interaction (Box 8)
    Author: Wormley, D.N.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: MIT
  - Potential for High-Speed Maglev Transportation: Application of Superconductor Technology to Intercity Travel Needs, 1988 (Box 8)
    Author: Johnson, L.R., Et al.
  - Letter Report on Progress and Proposal for Continued Research on Lateral Force Problem in Superconducting Magnets, 1976 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Cornell Univ.
  - Safety of High Speed Levitation Transportation Systems, 1992 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Research and Management, Inc. for USDOT
  - Refining the Magnetic Forming Capability, 1972 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Naval Ordinance Station, Louisville, Kentucky
  - Design of a Force-Free Inductive Storage Coil, 1975 (Box 8)
    Author: Mawardi, O.K.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Los Almos Scientific Laboratory
  - Design of Force-Free Torodial Magnets, 1964 (Box 8)
    Author: Wakefield, K.E.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Princeton Univ.
  - ETF Magnet Design Alternatives (Structural Aspects) (Box 8)
    Author: Bobrov, E.S.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Francis Bitter National Magnet Laboratory, MIT
  - Magnetic Suspension and Balance System Advanced Study-Phase II, 1990 (Box 8)
    Author: Boom, R.W., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Madison Magnetics for Langley Research Center
  - The Virial Theorem and Scaling Laws for Superconducting Magnet Systems, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Kritische Bewertung eindimensionaler Finit-Element-Modelle für die LCT-Spule, 1981 (Box 8)
    Author: Messemer, G., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Kernforschungszentrum Karlsruhe GmbH
  - Design Practice and Operational Experience of Highly Irradiated, High Performance Normal Magnets, 1982 (Box 8)
    Author: Schultz, J.H.
  - Physical and Engineering Constraints for Tokamak Reactors and Helical Coils, 1982 (Box 8)
    Author: Potok, R.E., Et al.
  - A Superconducting Generator Design for Airborne Applications, 1979 (Box 8)
    Author: Gamble, B.B., Keim, T.A.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: General Electric Company, Corporate Research and Development
  - Local Mechanical Effects in the Design of the Superconducting European LCT-coil, 1983 (Box 8)
    Author: Zehlein, H.
  - Proposal for FTU, The Frascati Tokamak Upgrade, January, 1981 (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Comitato Nazionale Energia Nucleare, Associazione Euratom-cnen Sulla Fusione, Centro di Frascati
  - Preliminary Magnet Design for a Stellarator Fusion Reactor, March, 1981 (Box 8)
    Author: Van Sciver, S.W., Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Fusion Engineering Program, Nuclear Engineering Department, Univ. of Wisconsin Madison
  - TORFA, Toroidal Reactor for Fusion Applications, September, 1980 (Box 8)
    Author: Jassby, D.L.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Plasma Physics Laboratory, Princeton Univ.
  - Radiation Shielding of Space Vehicles by Means of Superconducting Coils, April, 1961 (Box 8)
    Author: Levy, R.H.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Avco Everett Research Laboratory for Ballistics Systems Division, Air Force Systems Command, USAF
  - Mechanische Probleme bei der Entwicklung und Erprogung einer großen supraleitenden Toroidalfeldspule, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Structural Analysis of the Magnet System for Mirror Fusion Test Facility, 1978 (Box 8)
    Author: Wohlwend, J.W.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Lawrence Livermore Laboratory
  - Characteristics and Performance of a Superconducting Bumpy-Torus Magnetic Facility for Plasma Research, 1973 (Box 8)
    Author: J. Reece Roth, Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Lewis Research Center, Cleveland OH
  - Stress Calculations for Cylindrical Magnetic Field Coils, 1967 (Box 8)
    Author: Kilb, R.W.
  - New Concepts for High Energy Rate Forming System, 1965 (Box 8)
    Author: Waniek, Furth, Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Advanced Kinetics, Inc.
  - Computation of the Stresses in the Retaining Rings of a Superconducting Magnetic Dipole, 1969 (Box 8)
    Author: Westendorp, W.F.
  - Maglev System Concept Definition(1 of 2), 1992 (Box 8)
  - System Concept Definition of a Superconducting Maglev Electromagnetic System, 1992 (Box 8)
    Author: Proise, M. Et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Grumman Corporation for USACE
  - Electromagnetic Levitation, 1965 (Box 8)
    Author: Laithwaite, E.R.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Proc. IEEE
  - The Current State of Development of Noncontacting Suspension and Propulsion Systems in Japan, 1977 (Box 8)
    Author: Kyotani, Y.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Technical Development, Japanese National Railways
  - Suspension Characteristics of Magnetically Suspended High-Speed Trains (Box 8)
    Author: Okuyama, K., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Hitachi Review
  - The Magneplane System, 1975 (Box 8)
    Author: Kolm, H.H., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Cryogenics
  - High-Speed Transportation via Magnetically Supported Vehicles. A Study of the Magnetic Forces, 1970 (Box 8)
    Author: Borcherts, R.H., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Ford Motor Co.
  - Magnetic Levitation Research Vehicle (Box 8)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Japanese National Railways
  - Preliminary Design for a Maglev Development Facility, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Final Report on The National Maglev Initiative, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Comparison of Major Parameters in Electrodynamic and Electromagnetic Levitation Transport Systems, 1992 (Box 9)
    Author: Brown, W.S., et al
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: The Charles Stark Draper Laboratory, Inc.
  - Side Force in Coil-Sheet Magnetic Levitation Systems, 1974 (Box 9)
    Author: Menendez, R.C., et al
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign
  - Influence of Guideway Flexibility on Maglev Vehicle/Guideway Dynamic Forces, 1992 (Box 9)
    Author: Daniels, L.E.
  - On the Stability of Rigid Current Loops in an Axisymmetric Field, 1969 (Box 9)
    Author: Tenney, F.H.
  - Eddy Current Heating of Irregularly Shaped Plates by Slow Ramped Fields, 1979 (Box 9)
    Author: Dresner, L.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Oak Ridge National Laboratory
  - Magnetic Forming Studies, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Design, Development and Manufacture of Improved Magnetomotive Forming Tools, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Maglev System Concept Definition- Final Report, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Interactions Between Magnetically Levitated Vehicles and Elevated Guideway Structures, 1992 (Box 9)
    Author: Wormley, D.N., et al
  - Your Guide to Understanding Electric and Magnetic Fields, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Operational Characteristics of the Reference Maglev Vehicle (Box 9)
  - Aerodynamic Forces on Maglev Vehicles, 1992 (Box 9)
    Author: Barrows, T, et al.
  - Noise From High Speed Maglev Systems (Box 9)
  - Linear Synchronous Motors for Maglev, 1993 (Box 9)
    Author: Thornton, R.D. et al.
  - Maglev System Concept Definition: Executive Summary, 1993 (Box 9)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Foster-Miller, Inc. for USDOT- FRA
  - Low Cost Propulsion for Maglev, 1992 (Box 9)
    Author: Thornton, R.D.
  - Compendium of Executive Summaries from the Maglev System Concept Definition Final Reports, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Maglev Guideway Route Alignment and Right-of-Way Requirements, 1992 (Box 9)
    Author: Carlton, S., Andriola, T.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Martin Marietta Corporation, Air Traffic Systems Division
  - Transit Planning and Research Programs, 1994 Project Directory, March 1995 (Box 9)
    Author: Drancsak, M.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: For the Federal Transit Administration, USDOT
  - Magnetic Levitation Transportation System Technology Assessment, 1990 (Box 9)
  - An Industry Perspective on Maglev, 1990 (Box 9)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Arthur D. Little, Inc.
  - Final Report on The National Maglev Initiative, September, 1993 (Box 9)
    Author: NMI Staff
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: USDOT
  - National Transportation Research Board, September, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Maglev-New York Times, 1987 (Box 9)
    Author: F.C. Moon
  - Newspaper Articles/Brochures (Box 9)
  - Mag-Lev Meeting/SUNY Buffalo, April, 1987 (Box 9)
    Author: F.C. Moon, Kolm, H., et al.
  - NRC/TRB Report on High Speed Transit, March, 1996 (Box 9)
  - NMI/NRC/TRB Mag-Lev Meetings, December, 1992 (Box 9)
  - NRC/TRB, September, 1992 (Box 9)
  - NRC Transportation Brd, December, 1991 (Box 9)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: TRB/NRC
  - TRB Meeting, April, 1992 (Box 9)
  - F.C. Moon Testimony to Senate Committee, June, 2005 (Box 9)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: U.S. Senate Committee on Enviroment and Public Works
  - High Speed Transportation- German System, June, 2005 (Box 9)
  - Maglev- Japan, Y. Kyotani Papers (Box 9)
  - The Magneplane: Making Interstate Highways Safe at Two Hundred (Box 9)
    Author: Kolm, H.H.
  - Preliminary Design Studies of Magnetic Suspensions for High Speed Ground Transportation, March, 1973 (Box 9)
    Author: Reitz, John R., Robert H. Borcherts, L.C. Davis, T.K. Hunt, Dennis F. Wilkie
  - Superconducting Magnetic Levitation and Linear Syncronous Motor Propulsion for High Speed Guided Ground Transportation, March, 1975 (Box 9)
    Author: Atherton, David L.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Canadian Institute of Guided Ground Transport, Queen's University at Kingston, Ontario
- Series XII. Magnetic Fusion Superconducting Magnet Design Reports
  - Witamir-I Tandem Mirror Reactor Design, September, 1980 (Box 10)
    Author: Badger, B., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Fusion Engineering Program, Nuclear Engineering Department, University of Wisconsin, Madison
  - Uwmak-II-A Conceptual Tokamak Reactor Design, October, 1975 (Box 10)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Nuclear Engineering Department, University of Madison, Wisconsin
  - Uwmak-III-A Noncircular Tokamak Power Reactor Design, July, 1976 (Box 10)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Fusion Feasibility Study Group, Fusion Technology Program, Nuclear Engineering Department, University of Wisconsin, Madison
  - Uwtor-M-A Conceptual Modular Stellarator Power Reactor, October, 1982 (Box 10)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Fusion Engineering Program and Torsatron-Stellarator Laboratory, University of Wisconsin, Madison
  - Stresses in Magnets, Report Bibliography, February 14, 1974 (Box 10)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: United States Department of Defense Documentation Center
  - The Superconducting Magnet System for the Argonne 12-Foot Bubble Chamber, Design Report, June, 1968 (Box 10)
    Author: Marston, P.G., et al.
  - Computational Model for Superconducting Toroidal-Field Magnets for a Tokamak Reactor, August, 1977 (Box 10)
    Author: Turner, L.R. and M.A. Abdou
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Fusion Power Program, Argonne National Laboratory
  - Tokamak Experimental Power Reactor Studies, June, 1975 (Box 10)
    Author: Stacey, Weston M Jr., et al.